pazera-software.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Pazera-Software.com

Pazera Jacek software company ("we"), and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

## Personal information

WE DO NOT COLLECT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION 

## Cookies

We do not use cookies, but third parties, such as our advertisers, may use cookies to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. If you want to opt out of our third-party advertiser’s (Google Adsense) use of cookies, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

## Log files

As with most other websites, we use tracking tools to recognize our visitor’s browser name and version, IP address, referral page, etc. This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and is not used to identify individuals. 

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

## Privacy contact information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, you may contact us using the information given in the section Contact. 

## Changes

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
